<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Methods of Data Science I</title>
    <link>https://data-science-methods.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Methods of Data Science I</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://data-science-methods.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reminders for next week</title>
      <link>https://data-science-methods.github.io/2021-09-17-reminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://data-science-methods.github.io/2021-09-17-reminder/</guid>
      <description>Two things for next week.
  Class on Tuesday will be in SSM 317. This is the conference room in the middle of the floor, in the upper half of the mini-building. I’ll send out another reminder on Monday.
  Between Tuesday and Thursday, I’m going to ask you to find 5 papers in your field and examine the Data sections (or the data part of the Methods section or whatever they do) in light the discussion we’re going to have on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab due dates</title>
      <link>https://data-science-methods.github.io/2021-09-07-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://data-science-methods.github.io/2021-09-07-labs/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had a few questions about when the labs are due, and realized I forgot to make this explicit. Sorry about that!
There are no particular due dates for the labs. They have different lengths and levels of difficulty, and some of you will be working in pairs (hopefully everyone!) while others are working individually. And the amount of time you have to work on the lab might change from week to week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First day of class</title>
      <link>https://data-science-methods.github.io/2021-08-23_first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://data-science-methods.github.io/2021-08-23_first-day/</guid>
      <description>As part of the fallout from the Merced Station housing crisis, campus has delayed synchronous class meetings until August 30. For our class, this means we&amp;rsquo;re missing the first day.
We&amp;rsquo;ll try to make up for this lost meeting by moving a little faster than planned through the first few weeks.
Please be ready to hit the ground running when we meet for the first time next Tuesday, August 31:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://data-science-methods.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://data-science-methods.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
